Shawn Conerton

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Contact Details

Mobile: 815-257-3719 conerton52@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/shawnconerton/ https://github.com/conerton

Education

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp

Projects

Cori's DogFight - Front End Capstone

I created an app for a local Nashville business, Cori's DogHouse, so their costumers to track their hot dog consuming process. https://github.com/conerton/dogfight

- App has full CRUD functionality and was creating using React..
- I used CSS and React Bootstrap for styling for an easy user interface.

About

Moving to Nashville from rural Illinois has been a interesting journey. Over the last 7 years of working odd jobs from Event Lighting, service industry work and being a professional songwriter has given me a Swiss army knife book of skills that helps me with my new path, coding. Now starting on my new career of software development through the teaching of Nashville Software School has pushed me to new feats of what I feel like I am able to accomplish. From organization and communication skills- to problem solving like I have never done before.

Software Experience

TECHINCAL EDUCATION

Nashville Software School • 2020 - 2021

- Learn new languages in a group setting has taught me a whole new skill set. A six month nose to the grindstone environment has prepared me for the real life work
- Constant commits and pushes with GitHub
- Group projects provide experience to work with others
- Using Git and GitHub in a team setting
- Learning in a work-based environment.
- Emphasis on team-based development.
- Applied knowledge of interpreting existing code.
- Integrating remote and local API
- React, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, Python

Professional Experience

LIGHTING CREW LEAD

Nashville Event Lighting • 2016 - 2019

- Lead a team to accomplish clients goals
- Communicated with clients to fit their needs
- Problem solved with a team under strict deadlines

PROFESSIONAL SONGWRITER

Downtown Music Publishing • 2014 - 2016

- To keep an organized schedule
- Send emails in a professional environment
- Worked with a diverse group of people